{
    "test": [
        {
            "question": "В каком году была война 1812 года?",
            "response": "1812"
        },
        {
            "question": "Кто написал 'Войну и мир'?",
            "response": "Толстой"
        },
        {
            "question": "В каком году была война 1812 года?",
            "response": "1812"
        },
        {
            "question": "Кто написал 'Войну и мир'?",
            "response": "Толстой"
        },
        {
            "question": "В каком году была война 1812 года?",
            "response": "1812"
        },
        {
            "question": "Кто написал 'Войну и мир'?",
            "response": "Толстой"
        },
        {
            "question": "В каком году была война 1812 года?",
            "response": "1812"
        },
        {
            "question": "Кто написал 'Войну и мир'?",
            "response": "Толстой"
        },
        {
            "question": "В каком году была война 1812 года?",
            "response": "1812"
        },
        {
            "question": "Кто написал 'Войну и мир'?",
            "response": "Толстой"
        }
    ]
}